I carry high my craven flag,
my ally I'm gonna fly and let my
struggles shoot me through the sky!
It'd be a pity if we
lingered here and let our
pretty sparks of life
blend aloud and disappear?
There may be fog that even you can't
navigate If someone strong like you is lost,
then who will set me straight?
Cause when the waves
cast, my heart exists.
It's been your kindness and your strength.
That would free me from the mist.
And just like that.
We move on.
Sail to a new dawn.
Weigh anchor, ride as high as you can.
I assure I don't need anger.
I go fast as I am, yeah.
I hear you laughing like
you're numb to it all.
While we're dashing together.
No, we're never gonna fall, you know.
The whole world may now be my enemy.
Water swirl, but I ain't backing
down so long as I'm free, yeah.
Thought I'd give it, come
round the current with me.
All in, wake up bright and
early, making for the peak we go.
The battle atop the
Skulldome has come to an end.
The winner was previously Carrot,
but now the outcome has changed.
Look at me.
Help me!
Whoa, I gotcha.
You guys really did it!
You saved the land of Wano!
You were amazing!
I'm so happy!
The skyboats are flying.
I haven't seen this sight in years.
Oh, right.
Listen, everyone.
We've won.
Luffy defeated Kaido and
buried him deep in the ground.
The capital is safe at last.
Lord Momonosuke turned into a dragon
and stopped Onigashima from falling.
Isn't that right?
Sure is.
That dragon was Lord Momonosuke?
How is that even possible?
A Devil Fruit?
Twenty long years we have waited.
The vengeance in our hearts has burned
hotter, brighter than any flame.
Until this day.
It is our victory!
I really thought we were all going to die!
It's a miracle!
Oh, no, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Okay.
Yeah!
Always feels good to hunt big game.
Well, I feel like crap.
Oh my goodness!
You're alive!
So happy!
Enough!
Get off of me!
Shia really won?
That crazy rubber bastard!
We did it!
Let me be creative!
We'll be proud! Hooray!
I think he can do it!
We'll tell him that we won!
He said it!
Everyone pushed themselves to the limit.
I feel like my job's only starting.
Over here!
They soon need your help right away!
Chopper, help!
Zoro's out and he won't wake up! Dr.
Chopper, please help us! Okay. Dr.
Chopper, we need you here too! Dr.
Chopper, the wound
reopens! Dr. Please! Dr.
Chopper, you're not dying!
Miyagi, help me!
There are too many patients!
Don't worry!
We're here for you, Karoo!
Please, Karoo, the whole
castle for medical supplies!
I just hope we have enough!
Meanwhile,
in the capital, the Fire Festival comes
to a close as the skyboats float away.
Can I ask you a question?
Of course. What is it?
I heard my dad used to be real important.
He knew he'd die if he got caught,
and that's just what happened.
But he didn't get tricked or anything.
They said he got caught on purpose.
Why wouldn't my daddy do that?
Well...
Lord Yasui wanted to give
us a chance to fight.
He wanted to save our country.
If he hadn't made that decision,
every little flame of
hope that we lit over
the last 20 years would
have been snuffed out.
Cover your children.
Dies for now.
The final Dome to serve Kozuki.
Or rather, the happy-go-lucky fool
from Evisutau makes his final journey!
His death was a noble sacrifice, one
that ensured the land of Wano's future.
He and his allies wanted
to create a country
where you could be safe
and happy every day.
He did all that for me?
Don't go! Don't go!
Don't go!
What have you done?
Did you eat that fruit?
Didn't I tell you never to eat those?
I-I'm-I'm sorry!
Don't go.
Could I have some too?
Ooh!
You've got some real talent!
Why, you'll be the best dancer
in the land of Wano someday!
You think? Yes!
Daddy, he just wants me
to live a happy life?
But of course!
Okay then, I'll change the message.
That look good to you?
It's wonderful.
I know he'll love it.
As a samurai, and as a father, there
could be no greater honor, no greater joy.
And away you go!
Zuneesha.
Zuneesha, can you hear me?
I have thought it over carefully.
We're not ready.
I won't open the borders yet.
I understand.
I will defer to your wisdom on the matter.
I have faith in you, friend.
I thank you.
I wouldn't celebrate yet.
Remember, we saw a number, you samurai.
Not too late to surrender,
or else we're gonna blast ya!
There's no way that Commander Kaido lost!
And an emperor's crew won't lose either!
Damn it!
They don't know when to quit, do they?
No, you punks wanna fight!
Like a bloody left in a snake!
That's enough violence!
Get off me, bro!
Space pirates, lay down your arms at once!
You not only lost to your enemy,
You would have died if not for their aid.
What are you trying to say?
When Kaido was defeated,
his clouds vanished.
Who do you think stopped
this island from falling?
Kozuki Momonosuke, the
leader of our troops!
So what you're saying is your enemy now?
That will be your decision.
You awano your lives if you bare
your fangs at Lord Momonosuke.
I'll be happy to take what he's due!
What's happening? An earthquake?
The whole island is shaking!
What the hell is going on?
Babanuki, sir! What is it?
Something's happening in the sea!
No shit!
Put it on the screen!
Yes, sir!
That's one damn thing after another!
Don't just stand there, you idiots!
Go check on it already!
The battle in the sky has come to an end.
The winner, previously Kaido,
is now Straw Hat Luffy.
An eruption?
It was close to Udon.
That must have been the
rumble we just felt!
This can't be a coincidence!
It must be Kaido!
Up there!
Something's coming his way!
There is no need to worry!
This is not a crisis!
It's Kaido! But why?
Why?
This isn't fair!
This is the only day of the year
we're free from that monster!
Everyone, listen!
I am not Kaido!
The battle is over!
That eruption was nothing more
than Kaido's final farewell!
The leader of the Beast
Pirates has fallen!
The dragon just disappeared!
What's that?
It's a person.
How many of them are there?
But we just had her
funeral are you telling me
that she's a ghost this
must be some kind of trick
Boss Yoshido wait what
happened to your pompadour?
Forgive me.
It's a long story.
How is this possible?
It can't be.
Run for it!
Wait, you've got it all wrong. Stop!
There's no need to run away.
The dragon wasn't him.
It's not Kaido!
You mean there are two dragons?
Boss Kiyoshino!
Lady Komurasaki?
That looks just like her, but...
What's going on in front of the castle?
Boss Kiyoshino, you gotta explain!
The two of you have become quite famous.
But I wonder if they'll
remember the rest of us.
It has been 20 years after all.
What?
No, it's that!
Sir Kin'emon!
Foxfire Kin'emon? But how?
I thought he was dead!
They said he burned along with the castle!
This must be a dream!
or some sort of trick!
Hey, we didn't die, did we?
Are we in the afterworld?
Dreaming or not, I
don't want to miss this!
I feel like something
amazing is about to happen!
The Yuga-suga!
The Kawamatsu Papa!
Sir Dog Storm!
Race of the Mist!
Sir Cat Viper and...
Lady Kikunojo of the Fallen Snow!
Paws, what is this all about?
To start, Napping Kyoshiro was a
false name to obscure my identity.
In truth, though my face has changed, I
am a member of the Akazaya Nine! Denjiro!
They're here in the flesh!
Legendary samurai!
They came back for us!
I never thought I would see the day!
Ever since I was little,
I thought they were dead!
Lady Toki was right!
Her last words were true!
This is one hell of a story!
Get the light scroll!
We need to broadcast this right away!
Let the whole country know!
It's a miracle!
A broadcast from the capital!
Something's happening at the palace!
Is this about the earthquake?
I thought the whole region was done for!
What's going on there's a
message from the Capitol
we're about to watch
now start off the light
scroll your kind of son yep
that's me you're looking
for a beat down stop
resisting you know we won
huh don't you try anything
funny because we are
super tired and we will
probably lose no no wait I'm
not your enemy I've been
following your story in
the newspaper for quite
some time though in person
you're a little more unusual
looking than i expected
are you really human you're
the one with horns bro
so you're kaito's son huh stand back nami
i'm coming to save you my name is yamato
but you may also call me kozuki odin today
i will be joining your
crew nice to meet you
You're a funny one.
Well, I don't personally object, but our
captain is the one who has the final word.
You'll have to run it by him first.
Yeah, of course.
I hope he's okay after all that.
The way he fought gave
me chills. It was great.
He was so free.
Just whoosh, bang, boom
all over the place.
It was incredible.
Hey let's get out of here.
Yeah we gotta go now.
We showed them no mercy.
They'll definitely do the same to us.
We're
not done.
I didn't say you could go.
I don't want to be slaves.
Young master don't move
or I'll pound your face.
Then don't you know it's
unbecoming of a soldier to flee?
You'll take this like a man! You hear me?
Seems like they're not our enemies.
Yeah, speaking of which, what's
going to happen to the two of them?
I forgot to say!
My power will wear off
when the same moon rises.
So, it'll take a whole month?
Yep, that's the deal.
Sometimes when the animals
turn back to normal,
they decide they don't
want to be friends anymore.
But others decide to hang
around and stay buddies.
Interesting.
Maybe it depends on their personality.
I guess, in the end, they just
choose whatever makes them happy.
Hee hee!
Come here, master.
Don't you worry.
I'll be happy if we can
stay just like this.
Marcelino, I'd be happy if
you stayed with me, too.
But not as a servant.
Maybe more like a mom.
That way, we can be together forever.
Are you okay?
Thank you, Master.
Thank you so much.
No matter what happens,
you've truly brought me joy.
I'm glad, but can you hold me
a little less tight, please?
I'm so happy for them.
I'm choking up.
Hey, guys, look.
They're kneeling down.
I think someone else is about to show up.
Hold on. Who's that?
It's been 20 years since my
father, Kozuki Oden, died.
Father?
It can't be.
You have endured many hardships,
but those days have come to an end.
The fire festival will continue.
You may carry on however you please.
But what did she say?
You may drink as much as
you like. Wait, really?
Well water will be free of charge.
The factories will not be
allowed to poison the land.
And no one shall live as a slave.
Is that Momo?
Your suffering is over.
Four more died at the factory today.
Might be me tomorrow.
Someone has to tell Otama.
Otama, I'm so sorry.
Your mother and father aren't coming back.
Mom, Dad, you can rest in peace, okay?
I'm going to be just fine, I promise.
Don't deal, you're tickling me.
Woven hats for sale!
Does anybody need a hat?
Quality guaranteed!
You won't find a better deal!
Do you need a new hat, sir?
I don't have any money.
Find woven hats for sale!
They'll protect you from the snow!
I'm sorry, I couldn't sew any hats, but
it's okay, I'll just try again tomorrow.
May I have a hat, please?
A tingle!
Are you an orphan?
You must stay strong.
Just a few years more,
the samurai of the Kozuki clan
will return to the land of Wano.
And the demons who took control of this
country will be brought to justice.
A tingle!
Hmm.
I'll work hard till then!
I'll be strong like the
samurai from the Kozuki clan!
All I gotta do is keep believing!
I'll be okay!
Tama?
What's wrong, Master?
Tama, I'm gonna make this a normal thing.
I swear that by the time we leave Wano,
it'll be a place where you can
eat as much as you want every day.
You need not fear Orochi or Kaido.
Their reign of terror is finished!
I traveled the seas and
made powerful new friends.
With the ninja pirate
mink samurai alliance.
We raided Onigashima.
Orochi, Kaido, and the beast pirates.
We faced all the evils that
threatened this country.
And in the end, we emerged victorious.
You mean you took on those
monsters and actually won?
We won't have to battle
on our team anymore?
We're not in a damned alliance.
Does this mean we're going
to be happy every day now?
Hooray! We got her!
I never imagined you could
escape from this nightmare.
Thank you!
Our fallen allies who helped us save
this land will never be forgotten.
Kin'emon, what should I do?
What else should I say to my people?
I think this is your time to show off.
Is there anything left in the
world that can scare you now?
The name that my father gave
me means peerless among men.
Under my rule, this broken land
shall become a paradise on earth.
Lend me your strength and let us
work toward this end together.
For I have traveled 20 years
through time to save this country.
From this day forth.
I, Kozuki Momonosuke, will
lead the land of Wano!
Mother, I will keep my promise to you.
Father, I will follow in your footsteps.
The Closity clan is back!
We have a real Shogun!
We've been waiting for you
for so long! Thank you!
I called my escape!
A new dawn breaks.
The warriors sheath their swords, and
flower petals flutter in the wind.
The land has summarized new leader, a
handsome young man of eight years old,
gazes to the sky.
He is not a man of great strength, But
he is loyal and kind like no one else.
Kozuki Momonosuke steps forth as
the Land of Wano's proud shogun.
With his samurai at his side, he
will forge his place in history.